Hello Hello Friends Welcome back to my channel
Beauty Music and so friends I
told you in this video from the beginning
that I will be reviewing some of its products so
if you haven't seen my letter
then you are fine I will give you the
link of it in the description box
so here I am reviewing Papaya Kajal and this
cream and this face cream so
friends please watch the video till the end do
not forget my video and if
you liked my video then please
like and share my video
and if you are a fan of my channel then please
subscribe to my channel and
press the bell icon so that
you will get all the notifications of my videos
so let's start the video the
first product is Gold Pipe this
Papaya Hair Gel Skin is light weight
and it is for better benefits and creative free
that some of its other ingredients are
mentioned here so you can check it here
so it has Crispy Olive Oil and
many more ingredients you
can check it here  Yes, it has a flight and you
friend, its price is Rs.75 and I
got it for Rs.159 and what all claims does it make,
so let me tell you, this cream
will remove your dark spots and
if there is tanning on your face, it will also
remove it, you
can apply it on your face if you want and you can also apply it on your hair,
it has multiple uses, so if you are
making a face pack,
you can use it in that too, so friends,
now let's talk about its packaging,
its packaging is very classy,
I like it very much, here it
comes with lip balm, see,
if you use it after fragrance, then it is
very good, just
see its consistency, just like we use aloe vera
gel, we can use it in the same way, so
now I will apply it and show
you, so
friends, it is
not sticky at all, so it will get absorbed in your skin, that's a
good thing, it is not sticky that
when you apply something  The second product is
this Papaya Naresh Angels Cream Skin
Activator 6 grams from Good Wife and this too
is wings flight and creative free and
you can check its ingredients here,
so I will mention King Reliance on the screen,
you can check it easily and
here I have mentioned its factory gate
and the price is mentioned that it is flight
and its size is 220 ₹5 sugar candy mixed in it, there is
always a discount in Purple for 152
and what it does is it removes all the
dark spots on your face,
dark spots that appear due to pimples and
blemishes,
and it is also written in it that it
suits all skin types but it is highly
recommended for oily skin [
music]
so let's check its consistency,
this is a
scrub in water form, it also comes in cream form,
so I am taking a small amount of it
and I will show you how to apply it, so we will
Apply it on your face and use it
in circular motion so that it will
remove all the dead skin cells and your face will glow.
You must apply this scrub at least
twice a week for a
good result. It can suit all skin
types, so all skin types can
use it, but it is
highly recommended for oily skin.
Talking about the best product,
this is A Good Wife's Papaya Hydrating
Face Wash Cream Night Shift Cream. This is also non-
perfume and sulfate-free and it does
not contain minerals, there are no half chemicals
that will damage your face.
Its ingredients are here,
you can check it and its price is
twenty-five rupees, I got it for 152, its
prices are 152, so what it does is
it cleanses and hydrates your skin,
remember this and it
uses a lot of fresh ingredients, which will give
you a very  It will give a refreshing feel, it will give a replacement
feel,
so let's now talk
about its consistency, if we
talk about its fragrance then the milk
is just pregnant and look at its colour, it is
of this colour, light yellow, this
cream is of this colour, now I will apply it and tell you,
this cream suits all skin types
but it is highly recommended for dry
skin, so friends, this cream is not oily at all
but it is 1 minute for dry skin,
using this cream will keep your face
hybrid, friends, I hope you
liked this review of my product, if you liked it
then like
and share the video and thanks for
watching